<Namespace Name="Microsoft.SqlServer.Server">
  <Docs>
    <summary><span data-ttu-id="5b21e-101"><see cref="N:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server" /> 命名空間包含類別、介面和列舉型別，專門用於 Microsoft .NET Framework Common Language Runtime (CLR) 與 Microsoft SQL Server 的整合以及 SQL Server 資料庫引擎處理序執行環境。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="5b21e-101">The <see cref="N:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server" /> namespace contains classes, interfaces, and enumerations that are specific to the integration of the Microsoft .NET Framework common language runtime (CLR) into Microsoft SQL Server, and the SQL Server database engine process execution environment.</span></span></summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="5b21e-102">使用屬性中的類別<xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server>命名空間中，您可以建立預存程序、 觸發程序、 使用者定義型別、 使用者定義函數 （純量和資料表值） 和使用者定義彙總函式中任何支援的.NET Framework語言。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="5b21e-102">Using the attribute classes in the <xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server> namespace, you can create stored procedures, triggers, user-defined types, user-defined functions (both scalar and table-valued), and user-defined aggregate functions in any supported .NET Framework language.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="5b21e-103">您也可以在 SQL Server 中註冊它們。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="5b21e-103">You can also register them in SQL Server.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="5b21e-104">查詢<xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server.SqlContext>類別以決定是否要將目前執行的程式碼執行於 SQL Server 資料庫引擎處理序。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="5b21e-104">Query the <xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server.SqlContext> class to determine whether the currently executing code is running in the SQL Server database engine process.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="5b21e-105">這也讓呼叫端的內容，當使用者在伺服器上，呼叫 managed 預存程序或函式或使用者的動作就會引發 managed 程式碼的觸發程序。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="5b21e-105">This also provides the caller's context when a user calls a managed stored procedure or function on the server, or when a user's action fires a managed code trigger.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="5b21e-106"><xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server.SqlContext>類別提供<xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server.SqlPipe>物件，透過此結果傳回至用戶端從預存程序，<xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server.SqlTriggerContext>物件，它提供造成引發觸發程序的作業相關資訊，以及<xref:System.Security.Principal.WindowsIdentity>物件，可用來判斷呼叫的用戶端的身分識別，用戶端會使用整合式的安全性來進行驗證。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="5b21e-106">The <xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server.SqlContext> class provides a <xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server.SqlPipe> object, through which results are returned to the client from a stored procedure, a <xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server.SqlTriggerContext> object, which provides information about the operation that caused a trigger to be fired, and a <xref:System.Security.Principal.WindowsIdentity> object, which can be used to determine the identity of the calling client when the client used integrated security for authentication.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="5b21e-107">如需有關 SQL Server CLR 整合和中的 Api<xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server>命名空間，請參閱 SQL Server 線上叢書 》。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="5b21e-107">For more information about SQL Server CLR integration and the APIs in the <xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server> namespace, see SQL Server Books Online.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
  </Docs>
</Namespace>