<Namespace Name="System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement">
  <Metadata>
    <Meta Name="ms.openlocfilehash" Value="fefc91ccc5056e6a3e0640141b2ea2b1dffd83da" />
    <Meta Name="ms.sourcegitcommit" Value="df6cf590aa3087f6c7c202712eee781c6a3c8f96" />
    <Meta Name="ms.translationtype" Value="HT" />
    <Meta Name="ms.contentlocale" Value="zh-TW" />
    <Meta Name="ms.lasthandoff" Value="05/10/2018" />
    <Meta Name="ms.locfileid" Value="30734722" />
  </Metadata>
  <Docs>
    <summary>
      <span data-ttu-id="c5047-101">
        <see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /> 命名空間提供跨下列多個主體存放區之使用者、電腦和群組安全性主體的統一存取和管理：Active Directory 網域服務 (AD DS)、Active Directory 輕量型目錄服務 (AD LDS) 和 Machine SAM (MSAM)。</span>
      <span class="sxs-lookup">
        <span data-stu-id="c5047-101">The <see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /> namespace provides uniform access and manipulation of user, computer, and group security principals across the multiple principal stores: Active Directory Domain Services (AD DS), Active Directory Lightweight Directory Services (AD LDS), and Machine SAM (MSAM).</span>
      </span>
      <span data-ttu-id="c5047-102">
        <see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /> 會管理目錄物件而不區分 <see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices" /> 命名空間。</span>
      <span class="sxs-lookup">
        <span data-stu-id="c5047-102">
          <see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /> manages directory objects independent of the <see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices" /> namespace.</span>
      </span>
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="c5047-103">受管理的目錄服務應用程式可以利用<xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement>API 來簡化管理的使用者、 電腦與群組原則。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="c5047-103">Managed directory services applications can take advantage of the <xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement> API to simplify management of user, computer and group principals.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="c5047-104">先前需要冗長的程式碼，例如尋找使用者所屬的所有群組之存放區的複雜知識的解決方案幾行程式碼中完成<xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement>應用程式開發介面。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="c5047-104">Solutions that previously required intricate knowledge of the store or lengthy code, such as finding all groups to which a user belongs, are accomplished in a few lines of code with the <xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement> API.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="c5047-105">下列功能位於<xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement>API:</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="c5047-105">The following features are available on the <xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement> API:</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="c5047-106">基本目錄作業，例如建立和更新安全性主體已經過簡化。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="c5047-106">Basic directory operations such as creating and updating security principals is simplified.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="c5047-107">應用程式需要較少知識基礎的存放區來執行這些作業。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="c5047-107">The application requires less knowledge of the underlying stores to perform these operations.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="c5047-108">應用程式可以擴充以包含新類型的目錄物件的物件模型。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="c5047-108">Applications can extend the object model to include new types of directory objects.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="c5047-109">帳戶管理工作，例如啟用和停用使用者帳戶，進而簡化。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="c5047-109">Account management tasks, such as enabling and disabling a user account, are simplified.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="c5047-110">交叉存放區支援可讓 Active Directory 網域服務 (AD DS)、 Active Directory 輕量型目錄服務 (AD LDS) 和機器 SAM (MSAM) 資料庫，以包含成員從不同類型的存放區中的群組物件。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="c5047-110">Cross-store support allows group objects in the Active Directory Domain Services (AD DS), Active Directory Lightweight Directory Services (AD LDS), and Machine SAM (MSAM) databases to contain members from different types of stores.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="c5047-111">查詢範例搜尋，用於<xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement.PrincipalSearcher>類別，可讓主體物件上設定屬性，並搜尋其他物件，包含相符的屬性值與所選的市集的應用程式。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="c5047-111">Query by example searching, available on the <xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement.PrincipalSearcher> class, enables applications to set properties on a principal object and search the selected store for other objects that contain matching property values.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="c5047-112">增強型的搜尋電腦、 使用者和群組原則物件可讓應用程式搜尋相符的主要物件所選的存放區。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="c5047-112">Enhanced search on computer, user and group principal objects enables applications to search the selected store for matching principal objects.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="c5047-113">遞迴搜尋，用於群組的主體物件，可讓應用程式群組以遞迴方式搜尋，並傳回主體物件必須是分葉節點。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="c5047-113">Recursive search, available on the group principal object, enables applications to search a group recursively and return only principal objects that are leaf nodes.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="c5047-114">針對機器 SAM、 AD DS 與 AD LS 的存放區的認證驗證就較為簡單。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="c5047-114">Credential validation against the Machine SAM, AD DS, and AD LS stores is simplified.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="c5047-115">使用快速並行繫結 (FSB) 功能可用時，會增加連線速度。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="c5047-115">Connections speeds are increased by using the Fast Concurrent Bind (FSB) feature when available.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="c5047-116">連接快取可以減少使用的連接埠號碼。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="c5047-116">Connection caching decreases the number of ports used.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
    <altmember cref="N:System.DirectoryServices" />
  </Docs>
</Namespace>