<Namespace Name="System.ServiceProcess">
  <Docs>
    <summary><span data-ttu-id="f388a-101"><see cref="N:System.ServiceProcess" /> 命名空間提供可以讓您實作、安裝和控制 Windows 服務應用程式的類別。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f388a-101">The <see cref="N:System.ServiceProcess" /> namespace provides classes that allow you to implement, install, and control Windows service applications.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="f388a-102">服務是長時間執行的可執行檔，它執行時不需使用者介面。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f388a-102">Services are long-running executables that run without a user interface.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="f388a-103">服務的實作牽涉繼承自 <see cref="T:System.ServiceProcess.ServiceBase" /> 類別和定義要在啟動、停止、暫停和繼續指令傳入時處理的特定動作，以及系統關機時要採取的自訂行為和動作。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f388a-103">Implementing a service involves inheriting from the <see cref="T:System.ServiceProcess.ServiceBase" /> class and defining specific behavior to process when start, stop, pause, and continue commands are passed in, as well as custom behavior and actions to take when the system shuts down.</span></span></summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="f388a-104">服務會使用 InstallUtil.exe 例如安裝公用程式來安裝。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f388a-104">Services are installed using an installation utility such as InstallUtil.exe.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="f388a-105"><xref:System.ServiceProcess>命名空間提供的服務資訊寫入登錄的安裝類別。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f388a-105">The <xref:System.ServiceProcess> namespace provides installation classes that write service information to the registry.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="f388a-106"><xref:System.ServiceProcess.ServiceProcessInstaller>類別提供內含類別可安裝元件的一般安裝中的所有服務。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f388a-106">The <xref:System.ServiceProcess.ServiceProcessInstaller> class provides an encompassing class which installs components common to all the services in an installation.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="f388a-107">每個服務，您建立的執行個體<xref:System.ServiceProcess.ServiceInstaller>類別來安裝服務特有的功能。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f388a-107">For each service, you create an instance of the <xref:System.ServiceProcess.ServiceInstaller> class to install service-specific functionality.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="f388a-108"><xref:System.ServiceProcess.ServiceController>類別可讓您連接到現有的服務和管理它或取得它的相關資訊。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f388a-108">The <xref:System.ServiceProcess.ServiceController> class enables you to connect to an existing service and manipulate it or get information about it.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="f388a-109">這個類別通常用於管理功能，而且可讓您啟動、 停止、 暫停、 繼續，或在服務上執行自訂命令。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f388a-109">This class is typically used in an administrative capacity, and enables you to start, stop, pause, continue, or perform custom commands on a service.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="f388a-110">其中<xref:System.ServiceProcess.ServiceBase>類別會定義服務會執行命令時，處理<xref:System.ServiceProcess.ServiceController>是代理程式，可讓您呼叫服務上的這些命令。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f388a-110">Where the <xref:System.ServiceProcess.ServiceBase> class defines the processing a service performs when a command occurs, the <xref:System.ServiceProcess.ServiceController> is the agent that enables you to call those commands on the service.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
  </Docs>
</Namespace>