<Namespace Name="System.Diagnostics">
  <Metadata><Meta Name="ms.openlocfilehash" Value="ef6aeaebe2981ce7e1b191a089dab9ae242e488a" /><Meta Name="ms.sourcegitcommit" Value="434f60616a9793fa8436744549fc856e94f7a648" /><Meta Name="ms.translationtype" Value="MT" /><Meta Name="ms.contentlocale" Value="zh-TW" /><Meta Name="ms.lasthandoff" Value="08/24/2018" /><Meta Name="ms.locfileid" Value="30734992" /></Metadata><Docs>
    <summary><span data-ttu-id="7e203-101"><see cref="N:System.Diagnostics" /> 命名空間提供類別，允許您與系統處理序 (Process)、事件記錄檔和效能計數器互動。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7e203-101">The <see cref="N:System.Diagnostics" /> namespace provides classes that allow you to interact with system processes, event logs, and performance counters.</span></span></summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="7e203-102"><xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLog>元件提供功能來寫入事件記錄檔、 讀取事件記錄檔項目，並建立及刪除事件記錄檔和網路上的事件來源。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7e203-102">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLog> component provides functionality to write to event logs, read event log entries, and create and delete event logs and event sources on the network.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7e203-103"><xref:System.Diagnostics.EntryWrittenEventHandler>可用來以非同步的方式互動事件記錄檔。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7e203-103">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.EntryWrittenEventHandler> provides a way to interact with event logs asynchronously.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7e203-104">支援的類別提供存取權更詳細地控制，包括： 權限限制，能夠指定事件記錄檔類型 （這會控制的寫入事件記錄檔項目使用的預設資料類型），並逐一查看集合的事件記錄檔項目。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7e203-104">Supporting classes provide access to more detailed control, including: permission restrictions, the ability to specify event log types (which controls the type of default data that is written with an event log entry), and iterate through collections of event log entries.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7e203-105">如需有關這些工作的詳細資訊，請參閱 < <xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLogPermission>， <xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType>，和<xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryCollection>類別。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7e203-105">For more information about these tasks, see the <xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLogPermission>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType>, and <xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryCollection> classes.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="7e203-106"><xref:System.Diagnostics.Process>類別會提供在網路監視系統處理序，來啟動和停止本機系統處理序的功能。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7e203-106">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process> class provides functionality to monitor system processes across the network, and to start and stop local system processes.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7e203-107">除了擷取執行中處理序 （藉由指定電腦、 處理序名稱或處理序識別碼），或檢視目前的處理器的存取權的程序的相關資訊的清單，您可以取得處理序執行緒的詳細的知識，透過模組<xref:System.Diagnostics.Process>類別本身，並藉由互動<xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread>和<xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessModule>類別。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7e203-107">In addition to retrieving lists of running processes (by specifying either the computer, the process name, or the process id) or viewing information about the process that currently has access to the processor, you can get detailed knowledge of process threads and modules both through the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process> class itself, and by interacting with the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread> and <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessModule> classes.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7e203-108"><xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessStartInfo>類別可讓您指定各種用來啟動新的處理序，例如輸入、 輸出和錯誤資料流、 工作目錄和命令列的動詞命令和引數的元素。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7e203-108">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessStartInfo> class enables you to specify a variety of elements with which to start a new process, such as input, output, and error streams, working directories, and command line verbs and arguments.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7e203-109">這些會讓您精細控制您的程序的行為。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7e203-109">These give you fine control over the behavior of your processes.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7e203-110">其他相關的類別可讓您指定的視窗樣式，處理程序和執行緒的優先權，並與其互動之執行緒和模組的集合。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7e203-110">Other related classes let you specify window styles, process and thread priorities, and interact with collections of threads and modules.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="7e203-111"><xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter>類別可讓您監視系統效能而<xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory>類別可用來建立新的自訂計數器和分類。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7e203-111">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> class enables you to monitor system performance, while the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> class provides a way to create new custom counters and categories.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7e203-112">您可以寫入至本機的自訂計數器，並從本機和遠端的計數器 （系統以及自訂） 讀取。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7e203-112">You can write to local custom counters and read from both local and remote counters (system as well as custom).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7e203-113">您也可以取樣使用計數器<xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter>類別，並計算結果，從使用後續的效能計數器樣本<xref:System.Diagnostics.CounterSample>類別。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7e203-113">You can sample counters using the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> class, and calculate results from successive performance counter samples using the <xref:System.Diagnostics.CounterSample> class.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7e203-114"><xref:System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationData>類別可讓您在類別中建立多個計數器，並指定其類型。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7e203-114">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationData> class enables you to create multiple counters in a category and specify their types.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7e203-115">其他效能計數器元件相關聯的類別提供存取權的計數器、 計數器權限，而且計數器型別集合。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7e203-115">Other classes associated with the performance counter component provide access to collections of counters, counter permission, and counter types.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="7e203-116"><xref:System.Diagnostics>命名空間提供類別，可讓您偵錯您的應用程式，並追蹤您的程式碼的執行。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7e203-116">The <xref:System.Diagnostics> namespace also provides classes that allow you to debug your application and to trace the execution of your code.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7e203-117">如需詳細資訊，請參閱 <xref:System.Diagnostics.Trace> 和 <xref:System.Diagnostics.Debug> 類別。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7e203-117">For more information, see the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Trace> and <xref:System.Diagnostics.Debug> classes.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
  </Docs>
</Namespace>