<Namespace Name="System.Security.Authentication.ExtendedProtection">
  <Metadata>
    <Meta Name="ms.openlocfilehash" Value="b482f98a5c4316a191cd9beb8d2d226874520920" />
    <Meta Name="ms.sourcegitcommit" Value="df6cf590aa3087f6c7c202712eee781c6a3c8f96" />
    <Meta Name="ms.translationtype" Value="HT" />
    <Meta Name="ms.contentlocale" Value="zh-TW" />
    <Meta Name="ms.lasthandoff" Value="05/10/2018" />
    <Meta Name="ms.locfileid" Value="30735492" />
  </Metadata>
  <Docs>
    <summary>
      <span data-ttu-id="f956a-101">
        <see cref="N:System.Security.Authentication.ExtendedProtection" /> 命名空間支援應用程式使用擴充保護進行驗證。</span>
      <span class="sxs-lookup">
        <span data-stu-id="f956a-101">The <see cref="N:System.Security.Authentication.ExtendedProtection" /> namespace provides support for authentication using extended protection for applications.</span>
      </span>
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="f956a-102">某些認證挑戰回應的通用的這表示可以重複使用或轉送可讓您設計的整合式 Windows 驗證 (IWA)。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f956a-102">The design of Integrated Windows Authentication (IWA) allows for some credential challenge responses to be universal, meaning they can be re-used or forwarded.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="f956a-103">如果不需要此特定的設計功能的挑戰回應必須是所建構，最小值，目標的特定資訊，然後，在最佳情況下也某些通道的特定資訊。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f956a-103">If this particular design feature is not needed then the challenge responses should be constructed with, at minimum, target specific information and, at best, also some channel specific information.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="f956a-104">服務隨後即可提供延伸的保護，以確保認證挑戰回應會包含服務特有資訊 （服務提供者名稱或 SPN），並，必要時，通道特定資訊 （通道繫結 token 或 CBT）。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f956a-104">Services can then provide extended protection to ensure that credential challenge responses contain service specific information (a Service Provider Name or SPN) and, if necessary, channel specific information (a channel binding token or CBT).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="f956a-105">利用此資訊的認證交換中，服務就能進一步保護惡意使用的認證可能未正確取得的挑戰回應。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f956a-105">With this information in the credential exchanges, services are able to better protect against malicious use of credential challenge responses that might have been improperly obtained.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
    <altmember cref="T:System.Net.TransportContext" />
    <altmember cref="N:System.Security.Authentication.ExtendedProtection.Configuration" />
  </Docs>
</Namespace>